Guide to the Robert A. Hill Collection, 1890-2014 RL.10993
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research (RE), 1889-2012 and undated; 10
  - General, 1
    - Stewart, J.W., 1920-1930 (Box RE77)
    - Waddell, Ethel, 1938 Mar (Box RE77)
    - Wallace, William A., 1973 (Box RE77)
    - Williams, Vernal, 1923 Aug, 1940 Jul-1941 Mar (Box RE77)
    - UNIA Division list, 1988 (Box RE77)
    - Claude Barnett Papers, 1964-1987 (Box RE77)
    - Golos, 1920-1930, 1957, 1978 (Box RE77)
    - Moore, Richard B., 1932 Jan (Box RE77)
    - Negro World editorials on blacks and the Communist Party, undated (Box RE77)
    - Platform of the Communist International, undated (Box RE77)
    - Poindexter Resolution, 1919 (Box RE77)
    - Stokes, Rose Pastor, 1920-1928 (Box RE77)
    - Bilbo, Theodore Papers, 1938-1941, 1986; 2 folders (Box RE77)
    - Bilbo, Theodore Papers, used, 1938 Mar-Sep (Box RE77)
    - UNIA Bilbo Correspondence, 1938 Feb-1942 Sep (Box RE77)
    - Bilbo material documents, 1938 Aug-Sep (Box RE77)
    - Bilbo-Gordon correspondence, 1938 Jan-Oct (Box RE77)
    - UNIA Bilbo foreign correspondence, 1939 May-Aug (Box RE77)
    - Cox-Bilbo correspondence, 1939 Feb-1939 Sep (Box RE77)
    - Martinez-Bilbo correspondence, 1938 Apr-1939 Jun (Box RE77)
    - Fort-Whiteman, Lovett, 1919 Nov-1927 Jul (Box RE77)
    - Draper, Theodore - The Negro Question, 1924 Dec, 1934 (Box RE77)
    - Communism and the Negro Question, 1928-1930, 1972-1985 (Box RE77)
    - Glaberman, Martin and Mark Naison - Communist Party Articles, 1971, 1983 (Box RE77)
    - Communist Party in Harlem, 1930 Mar-1936 Jun (Box RE77)
    - Daily Worker clippings, 1925-1940 (Box RE77)
    - Russian article, undated (Box RE77)
    - Ferris, William H., editorial on Crusader and general research, 1921, 1987 (Box RE77)
    - 15th Regiment Armory, 1922 Jul 9 (Box RE77)
    - France, Senator Joseph, 1921 Apr (Box RE77)
    - Ford, Henry, 1922 (Box RE77)
    - Freethinkers, undated (Box RE77)
    - Sei Fujii, 1983 Apr (Box RE77)
    - Gandhi, Mohandas, 1922-1924, 1971 (Box RE77)
    - Garvey recording, 1921 Oct (Box RE77)
    - Garrett, John H., 1922 Aug, 1924 Jul (Box RE77)
    - Garvey's divorce decree, 1973 Jul, 1983 Jun (Box RE77)
    - Garvey, Marcus at Harvard, 1922 (Box RE77)
    - Volume II changes, 1922 Jun (Box RE77)
    - Green Star Line, 1923 Sep (Box RE77)
    - Griffin, Arthur, 1978 (Box RE77)
    - Grimes, W.W., undated (Box RE77)
    - Haiti, 1922 Apr-May (Box RE77)
    - Harris, George Wesley, 1932 Jun (Box RE77)
    - Haynes, S.A., 1922 Oct (Box RE77)
    - Heard, Bishop W.H, 1927 (Box RE77)
    - Hitchcock, Samuel M., 1939 Jan (Box RE77)
    - Howard, Perry, 1922-1923 (Box RE77)
    - Hodge, Henry, 1983 Jun (Box RE77)
    - Howard University debate, 1921 Dec 3 (Box RE77)
    - Research facsimiles, books and articles, 1917, 1926-1933, 1978-1983 (Box RE77)
    - Notes, 1988 (Box RE77)
    - Newspaper facsimiles, 1924, 1932-1934, 1988 (Box RE77)
    - Indexed, annotated newspaper articles and clips, 1889-1977; 2 folders (Box RE77)
    - Indexed, annotated newspaper articles and clips, 1922-1937 (Box RE78)
    - Africa and Garveyism, 1920-1931, 1981-1987 (Box RE78)
    - Unrest Among the Negroes, Report of the Coroner's Jury, 1919 Nov 3 (Box RE78)
    - Unrest Among the Negroes, Georgetown, British Guiana Riots, 1924 (Box RE78)
    - Unrest Among the Negroes, Report of the Commissioners Demerara and Berbice, 1935 Sep-Oct (Box RE78)
    - Unrest Among the Negroes, Conditions in the Caribbean Reserve, 1930 (Box RE78)
    - Unrest Among the Negroes, American Consulate Documents, 1937 (Box RE78)
    - Barbados Advocate Editorial and clippings, 1937 (Box RE78)
    - Barbados Advocate clippings, 1935-1939 (Box RE78)
    - National Archives correspondence, 1921-1989 (Box RE78)
    - Fiah, Erika, 1965 (Box RE78)
    - Portugal and Lusophone Africa, 1921, 1985 (Box RE78)
    - Muwamba, undated (Box RE78)
    - Natsoulas - Race Relations on Portuguese Africa: A Bibliographic Inquiry, 1981 (Box RE78)
    - Graham - Under Seven Congo Kings, undated (Box RE78)
    - Isaacman, Allen and Barbara - Mozambique, From Colonialism to Revolution, undated (Box RE78)
    - Mozambique, undated (Box RE78)
    - Diagne, Blaise, undated (Box RE78)
    - Kouyate, Garan, 1934 (Box RE78)
    - Renner, Alpha, 1922 (Box RE78)
    - Henderson, L.W. - Galangue: The Story of a Mission in Angola, 1986 (Box RE78)
    - Annotated newspaper clips, 1922, 1927-1929, 1940 (Box RE78)
    - UNIA chapters by state, 2010 Sep 4 (Box RE78)
    - Bibliography, undated (Box RE78)
    - References, 1969, 1978, 2003 (Box RE78)
    - Transcriptions, 1921 Feb-Apr, 1936 Sep 3 (Box RE78)
    - Marcus Garvey, research notes, 1971, 1977, 1979 (Box RE78)
    - Book references, 1964-1973 (Box RE78)
    - Garvey annotated research, 1983, 1988 (Box RE78)
    - Volume XIII documents, 1929, 1937 (Box RE78)
    - Hudson, Dr. H Claude, 1974 Apr-1983 Apr (Box RE78)
    - Hudson, Oscar, undated (Box RE78)
    - Independent Party of Color, Cuba, 1911 Feb-Mar (Box RE78)
    - Irish Liberty Bonds, 1969 (Box RE78)
    - Anglo-Irish Treaty, 1980 Mar (Box RE78)
    - Irish Treaty, 1921 (Box RE78)
    - Jamaican Legislative Council, 1921, 1926 (Box RE78)
    - Japanese Central Association, 1977 Aug (Box RE78)
    - Japanese Association, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Johnson, Adrian, undated (Box RE78)
    - Johnstone, Jack, 1983 Apr 7 (Box RE78)
    - Herbert, Julian, 1923 Mar-1932 Mar (Box RE78)
    - Laurier, Henri, 1913 Nov, 1983 Jun (Box RE78)
    - Lewis, Sir Samuel, 1979 (Box RE78)
    - Liberian Methodist, 1922 Oct (Box RE78)
    - Lincoln on Black Freedom, 1983 Mar (Box RE78)
    - Lewis, Robert Benjamin - Light and Truth, undated (Box RE78)
    - Freeman on lynching, 1916 Jun, 1983 Sep (Box RE78)
    - Kanawha in Cuba, 1924 (Box RE78)
    - Ku Klux Klan, 1921-1922, 1988 (Box RE78)
    - Ku Klux Klan, 1919 Dec-1925 Dec, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Maconey, A.H., 1922 Jan-Jun (Box RE78)
    - McCallum, T.S., 1922 Apr 8 (Box RE78)
    - McKane M.D., Alice Woodby, 1983 Apr 11 (Box RE78)
    - Maloney, Arnold Hamilton, 1924 Apr (Box RE78)
    - Manassas Institute, undated (Box RE78)
    - Mandate for Palestine, 1921 Nov (Box RE78)
    - Marcus Garvey v. New York Call, 1922 Aug (Box RE78)
    - Maram, Rene, 1922 Mar (Box RE78)
    - Mason, Madison Charles Butler, 1915 (Box RE78)
    - Mattuck, Maxwell S., 1922 Mar, 1957 Nov (Box RE78)
    - Men With Backbone, C.A. Wilson, undated (Box RE78)
    - Merrilees, Thomas P., 1921 May-1922 Jan (Box RE78)
    - Michael, Louis, 1978 Apr (Box RE78)
    - Moses, William, 1921 Oct (Box RE78)
    - Murray, Daniel Alexander, undated (Box RE78)
    - Muzumdar, Haridas, 1974 (Box RE78)
    - NAACP Executive Officers, 1921 (Box RE78)
    - Negro World Christmas Issue, 1921 (Box RE78)
    - Nautical Gazette, USA, undated (Box RE78)
    - Marconi, Guglielmo, 1922 (Box RE78)
    - Palestine Mandate, undated (Box RE78)
    - Paramount Trading Co., 1921, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Pickens, William, 1921-1922 (Box RE78)
    - Pickens, W.M. - Africa for the Africans, undated (Box RE78)
    - Plough Chemical Company, 1922 (Box RE78)
    - Pound, Roscoe, 1964 (Box RE78)
    - Prioleau, George W., undated (Box RE78)
    - Ramus, Esau, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Chicago Defender on Redding, 1921 (Box RE78)
    - Rising Tide of Color - Pan-Islam, 1921 (Box RE78)
    - San Francisco Japanese Chamber of Commerce, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Schnee, Albert Heinrich, 1935 (Box RE78)
    - Schnee, Heinrich article in New York Times, 1922 (Box RE78)
    - Seligman's article on Marcus Garvey, 1921 (Box RE78)
    - Sherrill, William, 1922-1932, 1954-1956 (Box RE78)
    - Seligman, Herbert, 1919-1920, 1978 (Box RE78)
    - Social Equality, 1921 (Box RE78)
    - Spewack, Samuel, 1971-1983 (Box RE78)
    - Spingarn, Arthur, 1925, 1937 (Box RE78)
    - Sterling, H.S., 1923, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Sweetser, Arthur, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Terry, Franklin Lee, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Thomas, James C., 1928-1929 (Box RE78)
    - Tobias, David E., 1911, 1922, 1972 (Box RE78)
    - Trotter, William, 1930 (Box RE78)
    - US in Santo Domingo, 1922 (Box RE78)
    - US Shipping Board, 1922 (Box RE78)
    - UNIA petition re: Dyer Bill, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - UNIA businesses, 1922 (Box RE78)
    - UNIA envoy to League of Nations, 1922 (Box RE78)
    - Vann, Robert, 1941 (Box RE78)
    - Walters, Alexander, 1915, 1917 (Box RE78)
    - Waring, Robert Louis, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Weal, James - The Next Emancipation, 1923 (Box RE78)
    - Phyllis Wheatley Hotel, 1922 (Box RE78)
    - White, Walter Fancis, 1955 (Box RE78)
    - Wells, H.G., 1921 (Box RE78)
    - Washington Disarmament Conference, 1971 (Box RE78)
    - Williamson, Oliver B., 1907-1934 (Box RE78)
    - Wolff, Julius, 1983 (Box RE78)
    - Zampty, Charles, 1921 (Box RE78)
    - Zayas, Alfredo y Alfonso, 1934 (Box RE78)
    - Zink, Albert vs. Black Star Line, 1921-1922, 1926 (Box RE78)
    - Bibliographic materials, undated (Box RE79)
    - Ranger, Terence - Traditional Authorities and the Rise of Modern Politics in Southern Rhodesia, 1989-1950, undated (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - British, 1925 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - correspondence between Garvey papers and Fascism specialists, 1985, 1998 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - criticism of socialists and communists, 1921, 1983 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - European (general), 1973 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - Garvey Movement, 1931, 1969 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - Garvey Movement on American, 1930 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - Garvey Movement on communists, 1932 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - Garvey Movement on European, 1937 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - Italian, 1921, 1936, 1972 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - miscellaneous nations, 1973, 1985-1986 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - research notes, undated (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - Bose, Subhas Chandra, undated (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - theory, 1974-1979 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - United States 1930s, 1940, 1960 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - United States Post WWII, 1985 (Box RE79)
    - German National Socialism, 1927-1937, 1978-1986 (Box RE79)
    - Jews and fascism, 1988-1990 (Box RE79)
    - Fascism - articles, 1925-1982; 2 folders (Box RE79)
    - Lamity, K. - The Harpoon, 1918 (Box RE79)
    - Whaley, Allen Weston, 1912-1921, 1978 (Box RE79)
    - Wheatley, Phillis, undated (Box RE79)
    - Wilcox, Ella Wheeler, 1902-1940 (Box RE79)
    - Williams, Charles Holston, 1923-1924 (Box RE79)
    - Williams, Reverend John A., 1913, 1922, 1980 (Box RE79)
    - Wilson, William B., 1980 (Box RE79)
    - Winslow, L. Lanier, 1921-1929 (Box RE79)
    - Wiseman, Sir William, 1920-1921, 1969 (Box RE79)
    - Woodfolk, R.W., 1979 (Box RE79)
    - The World, undated (Box RE79)
    - Wright, Edward, 1979 (Box RE79)
    - Wright, Richard Robert, 1910-1919, 1965-1967 (Box RE79)
    - Confraternity, 1920-1921 (Box RE79)
    - Firestone - annotations, 1921-1924, 1994 (Box RE79)
    - Butelezi, Elias - South African documents, 1989 (Box RE79)
    - Negro World articles, 1920, 1921 (Box RE79)
    - Gardner, John W., 1918-1930 (Box RE79)
    - Joyce, Maurice A., 1919-1931 (Box RE79)
    - Merrilees, Thomas P., 1916-1923 (Box RE79)
    - Gulley, Harry DeWitt, 1919-1928 (Box RE79)
    - Dunn, William, 1919-1925, 1984 (Box RE79)
    - Barnes, J. Edmestone, 2005 Dec-2008 Aug (Box RE80)
    - Rogers, J.A., undated (Box RE80)
    - Powell, John - White Citizen Councils, 1925 (Box RE80)
    - Harlan, Lewis, 1983-1984 (Box RE80)
    - Briggs, Cyril, 1933 (Box RE80)
    - Hope Experimental Station, 1909-1924 (Box RE80)
    - Scott, Emmet J., 1919 Aug-1980 May (Box RE80)
    - Hamdeoe, S.E.F.C.C. - The First Pan-African Conference of the World, undated (Box RE80)
    - Beta Israel (Falasha), 1928, 1993 (Box RE80)
    - DuBois, W.E.B. - The Negro's Fatherland, 1917 Nov (Box RE80)
    - Garvey, Amy Ashwood, edited by Lionel M. Yard - Portrait of a Liberator, Biography of Marcus Garvey - correction, undated (Box RE80)
    - Washington, Booker T., 1914-1939, 1958-1985; 2 folders (Box RE80)
    - Pan-African Conference, 1900, 1975 (Box RE80)
    - Williams, Sylvester H., 1896-1901, 1960 (Box RE80)
    - The Pan-African Conference 1900 - Hooker, J.R., 1974 (Box RE80)
    - The African World, 1920-1922 (Box RE80)
    - West Africa, 1920 (Box RE80)
    - Pass Laws - African Telegraph, 1919 May-Jun (Box RE80)
    - Bunyan, John, 1923-1926 (Box RE80)
    - Pan-African Congress - Gold Coast Leader, 1923-1924 (Box RE80)
    - Pan-African Congress Finances, Madam C.J. Walker correspondence, 1919 (Box RE80)
    - Pan-African Congress - Crisis - DuBois, W.E.B., 1919 Apr (Box RE80)
    - Gow, Rev. F.H. - Ethiopianism - George Carter NEH Application, 1985 (Box RE80)
    - Manchuelle, Francois - annotations, Delafosse and Kaidherbe, 1993 (Box RE80)
    - Sierra Leone officials - UNIA, 1920 Jun 20 (Box RE80)
    - Boyle, A.G. - Colonial Secretary, Southern Nigeria - African Telegraph, 1919 Jul-Aug (Box RE80)
    - Ladies, 1922-1923 (Box RE80)
    - Randall, Clarence, 1922 (Box RE80)
    - Marcus Garvey - Liberia, 1924 (Box RE80)
    - Black American missionaries, 1920-1922 (Box RE80)
    - Claparede, Rene-Edouard, undated (Box RE80)
    - Brown, Francis, 1922 (Box RE80)
    - Alcide, Thomas, undated (Box RE80)
    - Bellegarde, Dantes and Pan-Africanism - Phylon, 1981 (Box RE80)
    - African Times and Orient Review - advertisement, 1917 (Box RE80)
    - Grier, Sir Selwyn Macgregor, 1946-1957 (Box RE80)
    - McGuire, Bishop George Alexander, 1921-1986 (Box RE80)
    - Merriman-Labor, A.B.C., 1909-1919 (Box RE80)
    - UNIA - Petition to League of Nations, 1921-1922 (Box RE80)
    - Dean, Harry, 1925 Apr 17 (Box RE80)
    - Poston, R.S., 1932 Mar 3-31 (Box RE80)
    - Love, Dr. Robert J., 1900 Sep 1 (Box RE80)
    - Congo, 1931 Aug 10 (Box RE80)
    - Bridges, William, 1921 (Box RE80)
    - Prophet Elijah II of Nigeria and the gin trade, 1916 (Box RE80)
    - Ukpabi, S.C. - West Indian Troops and the Defence of British West Africa in the 19th Century, 1926 (Box RE80)
    - Thorne, Dr. J. Albert, 1987 Mar 18-May 20 (Box RE80)
    - Panama Canal, 1920 Jun 18 (Box RE80)
    - Negro Labourers in Cuba, 1922 (Box RE80)
    - Jamaicans in Panama, 1917 Jan 29 (Box RE80)
    - Grey, Edgar M., 1927 Mar 30 (Box RE80)
    - Briggs, Cyril - Africa Can Be Won, 1920 (Box RE80)
    - Obeah Cases, 1915 May-1958 Jun (Box RE80)
    - Hart, Richard, 2006 Jun 8 (Box RE80)
    - Lugard, Frederick Dealtry, 2006 May-Jun (Box RE80)
    - Bondelzwarts Rebellion, 1920, 1923 (Box RE80)
    - Chaswell, W.B., 1925 (Box RE80)
    - Gumede, Joseph T., 1921, 1978 (Box RE80)
    - Smuts, Jan, 1918-1919, 1924, 1029-1930 (Box RE80)
    - Selope-Thema, R.V., 1927, 1961, 1966 (Box RE80)
    - Rehoboth Bastards, 1925 (Box RE80)
    - Pass Laws, 1925 (Box RE80)
    - Mann, Tom, 1923 (Box RE80)
    - Loram, Dr. C.T., 1921 (Box RE80)
    - Lefela, Josiel, 1921 (Box RE80)
    - Cuban government investigation of UNIA, 1918-1949, 1998 (Box RE80)
    - Civilization, 1984 (Box RE80)
    - Braide, Garrick - Nigeria, 1996 (Box RE80)
    - Graham, William - Scotch Kirk, 1921, 1923 (Box RE80)
    - List of papers - Ethiopia, 1930, 1932 (Box RE80)
    - Pan-Noir, 1920 Oct 20 (Box RE80)
    - Catholic Apostolic Church in Zion, 1918-1923 (Box RE81)
    - Zambian Welfare Associations, 1979 (Box RE81)
    - Zambia, 1971 (Box RE81)
    - Zambia: Native Welfare Association, 2A 1/9/4s/1, 1930, 1931 (Box RE81)
    - Fields, Karen E. - Charismatic Religion as Popular Protest, 1982 (Box RE81)
    - Fields, Karen E. - Revival and Rebellion in Colonial Central Africa, 1976 (Box RE81)
    - Hastings, Adrian - John Lester Membe, 1945 (Box RE81)
    - Henderson, Ian - Pre-Nationalist Resistance to Colonial Rule in Zambia, 1970 (Box RE81)
    - Macpherson, Fergus - Anatomy of a Conquest: the British Occupation of Zambia, 1981 (Box RE81)
    - Prins, Gwyn - Millenarianism in Central Africa, 1987 (Box RE81)
    - Ranger, Terence - Making Northern Rhodesia Imperial, 1980 (Box RE81)
    - Johnson, Walton R. - Worship and Freedom: A Black American Church in Zambia, undated (Box RE81)
    - Zambia, 1965 (Box RE81)
    - Trotter, William Munroe, 1905-1920, 1973; 3 folders (Box RE81)
    - New Negro, 1919 (Box RE81)
    - Newspapers: African and European, undated (Box RE81)
    - Nkrumah and Mboya - Introduction, 1977 (Box RE81)
    - Pan-African miscellaneous, 1947, 1954, 1971 (Box RE81)
    - Parker, George Wells, 1918-1920, 1979 (Box RE81)
    - Phelps-Stokes, 1922 (Box RE81)
    - Reminders - Racialism on the Left E.D. Morel and the Black Horror on the Rhine, 1923 (Box RE81)
    - African Troops on the Rhine, 1921 (Box RE81)
    - Robinson, Ronald - The Moral Disarmament of African Empire, 1919-1947, 1979 (Box RE81)
    - Smith, C.S., 1918-1921 (Box RE81)
    - Thomson, Su Basil, 1921 (Box RE81)
    - Maps, 1967, 1985 (Box RE81)
    - Africa Maps: Region - National Geographic, 1943, 1954 (Box RE81)
    - McGuire, George A., 1920 (Box RE81)
    - McKay, Claude, 1919-1923, 1929 (Box RE81)
    - Meredith, David - The British Government and Colonial Economic Policy, 1919-39, 1975 (Box RE81)
    - Monroe Doctrine, 1972 (Box RE81)
    - Morel, E.D. - The Black Man's Burden, undated (Box RE81)
    - Moton, R.R. - Tuskegee Institute, 1918-1919 (Box RE81)
    - New Negro, 1899 (Box RE81)
    - Hopkins, Cain - Gentlemanly Capitalism, 1987 (Box RE81)
    - Jackson, George H., 1919 (Box RE81)
    - Langston Hughes introduction, 1940 (Box RE81)
    - Jamaica - political constitution, 1888-1889, 1920, 1955 (Box RE81)
    - African Series - Haynes, Dr. George E., 1930 (Box RE81)
    - Kaiser introduction, 1927 (Box RE81)
    - Lagrosilliere, Joseph, 1920 (Box RE81)
    - Madison Square Garden, undated (Box RE81)
    - British Consulate general correspondence, 1927 (Box RE81)
    - Nigeria, 1921 (Box RE81)
    - The Nigerian Pioneer - clippings, 1920 (Box RE81)
    - Abeokuta Historical annotations, 2006 (Box RE81)
    - Sam, Chief Alfred C., 1914-1917 (Box RE81)
    - Itab-Ethiopian War, 1934-1936 (Box RE81)
    - Julian, Captain - Italo-Ethiopian War, 1930-1935 (Box RE81)
    - Haile, Selassie - speeches, undated (Box RE81)
    - Ethiopian War - enlistment recruitment of Afro-Americans, 1934-1936 (Box RE81)
    - DuBois, W.E.B. - Inter-Racial Implications of the Ethiopian Crisis, 1935 (Box RE81)
    - Prince Imah Devount, Ishi Van Dova, 1923 (Box RE81)
    - Ethiopian Progressive Association, 1905-1919 (Box RE81)
    - Ali, Duse Mohamed, 1977-1984 (Box RE81)
    - Barber, J.D., 1922-1929 (Box RE81)
    - Ethiopia, 1918-1929 (Box RE81)
    - Ethiopian documents, annotations - Pat K. Comments, 1988 (Box RE81)
    - Asante, S.K.B. - Italo-Ethiopian Conflict: A Case Study, 1974 (Box RE81)
    - Asante, S.K.B. - Italo-Ethiopian Crisis, 1976 (Box RE81)
    - Van Velsen, J. - Some Early Pressure Groups in Malawi, 1966 (Box RE82)
    - Zeleza, Paul - Economic and Social Developments in Colonial Malawi, undated (Box RE82)
    - Malawi, 1927 (Box RE82)
    - Madagascar - Biography, 1989 (Box RE82)
    - Malagasy, undated (Box RE82)
    - South African newspapers, 1921 (Box RE82)
    - The South African Outlook, 1922 Mar 1 (Box RE82)
    - Southern African Research Program, 1980-1985 (Box RE82)
    - South Africa - reviews, 1972, 1975 (Box RE82)
    - Spooner, Rev. K.E.M., undated (Box RE82)
    - Liberia, 1923-1924 (Box RE82)
    - SubDivision of Stands in Townships, 1923 (Box RE82)
    - Swaziland, 1923, 1925 (Box RE82)
    - Thaele, James M., 1925, 1929 (Box RE82)
    - Thibedi, W., undated (Box RE82)
    - Townships, 1923 (Box RE82)
    - Trapido, S. - Liberalism in the Cape in the 19th and 20th Centuries, 1974 (Box RE82)
    - Tyamzashe, H.P., 1931 Jul 24 (Box RE82)
    - Umteteli wa Bantu, 1920, 1921 (Box RE82)
    - Evangelical Lutheran Mission, Transvaal, South Africa, 1898 (Box RE82)
    - UNIA Opposes South African Absorption of Protectorates, 1935 (Box RE82)
    - Walshe, A.P. - The Origins of African Political Consciousness in South Africa, 1969 (Box RE82)
    - Walshe, A.P. - Black American Thought and African Political Attitudes, 1970 (Box RE82)
    - West London Division, 1924, 1926 (Box RE82)
    - Wickins, P.L. - The Industrial and Commercial Workers' Union of Africa, review, 1920-1921, 1979; 2 folders (Box RE82)
    - Willian, Brian - The Anti-Slavery and Aborigines' Protection Society and the South African Natives' Land Act of 1913, 1979 (Box RE82)
    - Willian, Brian - The Gift of the Century, Solomon Plaatje, De Beers, etc., 1977 (Box RE82)
    - Van Onselen, Charles - The Witches of Suburbia - Domestic Service, undated (Box RE82)
    - Van Riebeeck, Johan, 1978 (Box RE82)
    - Vernon, Bishop W.T., 1909, 1921 (Box RE82)
    - Yergan, Max, 1921-1922, 1931 (Box RE82)
    - Worker's Herald, I.C.U., 1925, 1927 (Box RE82)
    - Yearwood, Ernest August, 1920 (Box RE82)
    - Worcester shootings, 1930 (Box RE82)
    - Thema, R.V. Selope and H.D.T. Tyamzashe - The Iniquity of the Pass Laws: The Plight of the Black Man, undated (Box RE82)
    - Woodstock Division, 1924-1925 (Box RE82)
    - Zionism in South Africa, 1927 Jul 9 (Box RE82)
    - South Africa - bibliography, 1942, 1979 (Box RE82)
    - Namibia - 1888-1984: 100 Years of Foreign Occupation, 100 Years of Struggle, conference (Box RE82)
    - VEM Material, 1921, 1924 (Box RE82)
    - Namibia (Swaga), undated (Box RE82)
    - Ludritz Division - Namibia, 1921-1925 (Box RE82)
    - South West Africa Administration - Namibia, 1922, 1925 (Box RE82)
    - South West African Archives, 1922-1925 (Box RE82)
    - South West Africa, 1923-1935 (Box RE82)
    - Namibia - 1888-1984: 100 Years of Foreign Occupation, 100 Years of Struggle, conference, 1964, undated (Box RE82)
    - South West Africa, 1984 (Box RE82)
    - Union of South Africa - Report of the Rehoboth Commission, 1927 (Box RE82)
    - Tanganyika Notes and News, index, 1961 (Box RE82)
    - Apter, David - The Political Kingdom in Uganda, 1961 (Box RE82)
    - Iliffe, John - A History of the Dockworkers of Dar es Salaam, 1970, 1975 (Box RE82)
    - Phiri, Hanock M. - Zambia, 1925-1926 (Box RE82)
    - Johnson, Walton - Worship and Freedom, 1979 (Box RE82)
    - African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1925, 1931, 1932-1936; 3 folders (Box RE82)
    - Information on Circulation of Subversive Literature, 1934, 1946-1947 (Box RE82)
    - Afrocentrism, 1991 (Box RE83)
    - Fraternal orders, 1983-1984 (Box RE83)
    - Fraternalism, 1921-1930, 1952, 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box RE83)
    - Freedom's Journals: A History of the Black Press in New York State, 1986 (Box RE83)
    - Higher Thought Articles, 1910, 1915, 1921 (Box RE83)
    - Tanna, Laura - Jamaican Folk Tales and Oral Histories, 1984 (Box RE83)
    - Jamaican folktales, trickster, 1957,1972, 1976 (Box RE83)
    - Garvey, Marcus - Manifesto of the UNIA, 1922 (Box RE83)
    - Mind Games in New England, 1973, 1987 (Box RE83)
    - Printers' strike, 1823-1927, 1967, 1971 (Box RE83)
    - Propaganda in its Military and Legal Aspects, undated (Box RE83)
    - Rogers, J.A.- Additional Facts on Marcus Garvey and His Trial for Using the Mails to Defraud, undated (Box RE83)
    - Set Girls, 1883, 1929, 1983-1984 (Box RE83)
    - Research Spain, John Hope, Turkey, 1921, 1967, 1993-1994 (Box RE83)
    - Alter, Robert - Rogue's Process: Studies in the Picaresque Novel, 1964 (Box RE83)
    - Success ethic, 1902, 1923-1929, 1930-1936 (Box RE83)
    - Picaresque novel, 1957-1958, 1964 (Box RE83)
    - The Split in the PNP, tribunal findings, etc., 1952 (Box RE83)
    - UNIA salaries, 1921 Aug 27 (Box RE83)
    - Willis, Deborah, 1991-1993 (Box RE83)
    - Archival Research - US State Department, 1945-1949 (Box RE83)
    - Trinidad and Tobago, 1919-1938 (Box RE83)
    - Black Star Line - SS Yarmouth, 2014 (Box RE83)
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1923 Feb (Box RE83)
    - Cox, S.A. Gilbert, editor, Our Own, 1910 (Box RE83)